{
    "subject": "resource/Lionel_Casson",
    "predicate": "property/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Classics",
    "human_readable": "Lionel Casson's occupation is Classics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8667142391204834,
            "question": "What is Lionel Casson's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8449990153312683,
            "question": "What are some possible career paths for someone with a background in Classics like Lionel Casson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6982473731040955,
            "question": "What academic field does Lionel Casson specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6618736386299133,
            "question": "Does Lionel Casson's occupation require strong language skills?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5438240170478821,
            "question": "In which subject area does Lionel Casson work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49032673239707947,
            "question": "Lionel Casson's work could contribute to our understanding of which historical periods?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4731740653514862,
            "question": "Lionel Casson's work likely involves studying which ancient cultures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3578791916370392,
            "question": "What kind of research might Lionel Casson conduct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35758981108665466,
            "question": "What types of texts might Lionel Casson analyze?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22364142537117004,
            "question": "What is the study of Classics focused on?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lionel Casson's occupation is Classics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3872_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What types of texts might Lionel Casson analyze?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3872_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of research might Lionel Casson conduct?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3872_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lionel Casson's work likely involves studying which ancient cultures?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3872_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3872_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3872_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3872_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3872_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3872_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3872_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3872_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3872_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3872_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3872_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, I can evaluate the triple as follows:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain several mentions of Lionel Casson being a professor emeritus at New York University and a specialist in classics, which suggests that his occupation is indeed related to Classics."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Lionel Casson is an Emeritus Professor of Classics at New York University, which supports the triple stating his occupation as Classics."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Lionel Casson's occupation was not just Classics; he was a professor emeritus of Classics at New York University, specializing in maritime history.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Information from the texts states that Lionel Casson was a professor emeritus at New York University, specializing in maritime history. While Classics encompass many areas of study related to ancient civilizations, including maritime history, his specific area of expertise points away from a purely classical focus.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information suggests that Lionel Casson's occupation includes Classics but also mentions \"ancient maritime history\", \"maritime travel\", and being a \"specialist in maritime history\" which implies his expertise extends beyond the field of Classics.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Lionel Casson's primary occupation as described in the context is Classics, but he also specializes in maritime history. He is referred to as \"a classicist\" and an \"emeritus Professor of Classics at New York University,\" yet his work also includes books on ancient maritime travel and ships. Therefore, labeling his occupation solely as Classics overlooks his expertise in another significant field.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}